Guide to the Martin Wong Papers MSS.102
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Artwork, 1982-1999; 3.5 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 4 oversize flat boxes.
  - Subseries II.A: Art by Wong, 1982-1999
    - Sketchbook, undated (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Color copies w/ sign language, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Pencil sketches; Pen & ink sketches, undated (Box 17, Folder 107)
    - Study: man in a suit (paint), undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Sign language pencil sketches (series), undated (Folder 2 Left)
  - Subseries II.B: Art by Others, 1982-1999
    This subseries contains artwork collected by Wong, featuring the work of John Ahearn and Mark Kostabi (copies only). Two portraits of Wong are also included.
    - Kostabi Mini-Figures (Copy), undated (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Drawing: "Trent & Revonda," by John Ahearn, undated (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Drawing: Portrait of a Man (Artist Unknown), undated (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Copy of John Ahearn's sketchbook, undated (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Painting: Artwork, Signed by R. Liderman, undated (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Drawing: Bellevue Hospital, by Sam, Feb 2 1986 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Drawing: Martin Wong, by R. Bokov, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Drawing: Martin Wong, by Lee, undated (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous Childrens' Artwork, undated (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Cartoon, by S. Hernandez, 8/2/89, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - "Fierce Pussy" series (copies; artist unknown), undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Series III: Source Material, 1951-1998; 7 Linear Feet in five record cartons, one manuscript box, four oversize flat boxes, and one flat file folder.
  Series III: Source Material is by far the largest series, and is comprised of imagery (not including oversize) inspirational to Wong. Magazines, posters, invitations to gallery events and parties, memorabilia, and graffiti materials comprise the series. Where possible, the series has been ordered alphabetically by theme - themes include boxing, prisons, firefighters, Chinatown, and sign language.
  This series is divided into two subseries based on language of material: Subseries III.A: Source Material and Subseries III.B: Asian-Language Source Material.
  - Subseries III.A: Catalogs, Graffiti, Invites, Posters, Source Material, etc., 1951-1998; 7 Linear Feet in five record cartons, four oversize flat boxes, and one flat file folder.
    Scope and Contents note
    Subject: Catalogs, Graffiti, Invites, Posters, Source Material & Source Magazines
    - Catalog: "An All-Star Salute to Chinese American Cultural Pioneers", 1993 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Catalog: "Art for Learning", 1994 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Catalog: "Daze," Artwork and Biography, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Catalog: "Longwood Arts Journal, 1992-1993, Bronx Council on the Arts" (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Catalog: "In the Looking Glass: Contemporary Narrative Painting", 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Catalog: Museum of the City of New York, Fall 1996 (includes Graffiti Symposium) (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Catalog: New Museum of Contemporary Art, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Catalog: "In the Ring", 1993 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Catalog: "Simon Says," Summer 1998 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Catalog: "The Curio Shop"/The Asian American Arts Network, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Catalog: "Martin Wong," Exit Art Show, 1998-11-1998-12 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Catalog: "Contemporary Art Auction to Benefit El Bohio", 1985-09 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Catalog: Jane Dickson, "Paradise Alley", 1996 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Catalog: Steven R. Miller, undated (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Graffiti: Tag Sketches, undated (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Graffiti: Aroc Tag Book, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Graffiti: Red Marker Tag Book, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Graffiti: Tags, drawings, and writings, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Graffiti: Paint Palette Tag Book, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Graffiti: Black Marble Tag Book, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Graffiti: Separated Cover Tag Book, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Graffiti: Cose Tag Book, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Graffiti: Spray Paint Tag Book, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Graffiti: Landscape Tag Book, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Graffiti: John Lennon Starting Over Tag Book, undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Graffiti: Laroc Tag Book, undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Graffiti: Deep Cover Posse Tag Book, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Graffiti: Black Spray Paint Sketchbook, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Graffiti: Puerto Rico Sketchbook, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Graffiti: Fun Gallery Sketchbook, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Graffiti: Frenzy Sketchbook, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Graffiti: Space Sketchbook, undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Graffiti: Property of Sketchbook, undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Graffiti: Cose The Death Squad Sketchbook, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Graffiti: PGA Crew Sketchbook, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Graffiti: The Master Artist Stash II Sketchbook, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Graffiti: TDS Lives Sketchbook (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Graffiti: Gremlin Sketchbook, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Graffiti: Fresh Kidd Rocs Sketchbook, undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Graffiti: Shield Sketchbook, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Graffiti: Lone Ranger Sketchbook, undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Graffiti: Subway Cars Sketchbook, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Graffiti: F5 by Lee Quiñones, undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Graffiti: Clippings, undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Graffiti: "Nab 2 as Transit Writers" (newspaper item), undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Graffiti: Artwork by Crash, Sharp, Laroc, 1985-1994 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      Many tags identified by Sean Corconan of the Museum of the City of New York.
    - Graffiti: Tag by Kies, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Graffiti: Stash Two Fax Art, 1989-05-03 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Graffiti: Layout and Labels for Graffiti Show, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Graffiti: Postcard and Photo, Keith Haring and LA2, undated (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Graffiti: Mini-notebook with Descriptions of Graffiti Art, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Graffiti: Print Magazine, "Spray-Can School", 1982 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Graffiti: "Art from a Spray-can" (manuscript draft), undated (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Graffiti: "Bizzama," signed "AMBH", undated (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Graffiti: Graffiti Form with Tags, undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Graffiti: "Whose to Say?" (painting by artist Jonathon), undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Graffiti: Hip-Hop Figure, undated (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Graffiti: Notes and Comment on Graffiti Art by Martin Wong, undated (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Graffiti: photo (color copy) of unidentified graffiti artists, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Graffiti: photos (of unidentified graffiti artists - ?), undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Graffiti: "Art Boom," no.2, 1991 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Graffiti: "Coming from the Subway," Groninger Museum, 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Graffiti: "The Subway Sun", 1987 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Graffiti: "Post-Graffiti" Catalog, Sidney Janis Gallery, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Graffiti: "Wild Style" (film) 3-D Logo, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Graffiti: "The Devastating Artist" (drawing), undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Graffiti: "Wild Style" (film) logo sketches, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Graffiti: "Wild Style" (film) Transcript, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Graffiti: "Wild Style" (film) Poster and Artwork, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Graffiti: "Wild Style" (film) Book and Audiocassette, "Hip Hop Rap Music in NYC", 1983 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Graffiti: "Wild Style" (film) Promo Flyers in Chinese, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Graffiti: Museum of American Graffiti Letterhead, Business Card, Grand Opening Invitation, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated (Box 12, Folder 80)
    - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - Graffiti: tag-book sketchbook, undated (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Graffiti: "Village Voice," Dec 24-30, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 85)
    - Graffiti: "New York Newsday," May 3, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 86)
    - Graffiti: "Aerosoland"/"Rockathon" Zine, undated (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Graffiti: Portrait of a Woman Photograph, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Graffiti: Mural Art Photograph, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Graffiti: Stabbing Mural Photograph, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Graffiti: "IGT" Zine, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Graffiti: "Fresh!" Painting, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Graffiti: color copy w/ tags, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Graffiti: "Martin" tag, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Graffiti: tag sketches, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Graffiti: "The East Village Eye", January 1982; February 1983 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Graffiti: "Craft International," Spring 1982 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Graffiti: "Wild Thing" Tag, undated (Box 17, Folder 86a.)
    - Invites: Gallery Openings and Shows, 1980s-1990s (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Invites: Gallery Openings and Shows, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Invites: Gallery Openings and Shows, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Invites: Gallery Openings and Shows, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Invites: Gallery Openings and Shows, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Invites: Gallery Openings and Shows, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Invites: Gallery Openings and Shows, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Invites: Gallery Openings and Shows, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Invites: Gallery Openings and Shows, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Invites: Gallery Openings and Shows, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Invites: Gallery Openings and Shows, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Invites: Gallery Openings and Shows, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 17-18)
    - Invites: Gallery Openings and Shows, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Invites: Gallery Openings and Shows, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Invites: Gallery Openings and Shows, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Invites: Gay and Lesbian Events, 1980s-1990s (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Invites: Social and Cultural Events, Parties, 1988-1996 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
    - Poster: "Virtual and Interactive Arts Symposium", 1992-02 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Poster: "Hallowe'en @ Roxy", 1992 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Poster: "2nd Annual Open Studio Chinatown Exhibition", 1986-05 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Poster: "Daze & Crash: New Works", 1990-05 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Poster: "Martin Wong, Semaphore East Show", 1985 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Poster: "Martin Wong, Semaphore", undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Poster: "Martin Wong: The Chinatown Paintings", 1983 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Poster: "The Saint at Large Presents Hallowe'en", 1994 (Flat-file-folder 1)
      Poster includes image of "Big Heat" by Wong.
    - Poster: "The Saint This Summer", 1987 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Poster: "The Saint Opening Night", 1987-09-26 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Poster: "Exit Art", 1988 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Poster: "The White Party", 1993 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Poster: "Signs of Life Panel Discussion", 1992 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Poster: "The Eighth Annual South Bronx Show", 1987 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - Source: assorted imagery (postcards, photos, etc.), undated (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - Source: "Time" photos (urban commerce series), undated (Box 13, Folder 114a)
    - Source: "My 6 Convicts" (book, c.1951) (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - Source: prison (assorted clippings), undated (Box 5, Folder 115a.)
    - Source: postcard of kissing firemen (cf. Big Heat painting), undated (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Source: African-American/black people, undated (Box 5, Folder 116a.)
    - Source: Chinatown materials & Chinese imagery, undated (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Source: Chinese imagery, undated (Box 13, Folder 117a)
    - Source: Shanghai Museum catalog, undated (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Source: Chinese litho cards, undated (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - Source: Chinese characters (script), undated (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Source: photo of Cupcake & Paco from "Short Eyes" (play) (cf. Annunciation painting), undated (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Source: sign language/the deaf, undated (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Source: astronomy/constellations, undated (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Source: boxing, undated (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Source: cowboy/western, undated (Box 5, Folder 124a.)
    - Source: firefighters, undated (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Source: Lower East Side/graffiti/tattoos, undated (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - Source: the male nude/gay erotica, undated (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - Source: men in uniform, undated (Box 5, Folder 127a.)
    - Source: Nora Wong material, undated (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - Source: California redwoods, undated (Box 5, Folder 128a.)
    - Source: works of art, undated (Box 5, Folder 128b.)
    - Source: Tattoo Wall Flash, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Source: "Rally to Save Firefighters" poster, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Source Magazines: art, undated (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - Source Magazines: art, undated (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - Source Magazine: art ("Artforum"), undated (Box 13, Folder 130a)
    - Source Magazines: "The Art Newspaper", 1992 January-February (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Source Magazines: Asian arts & culture, undated (Box 5, Folder 131)
    - Source Magazines: Asian arts & culture, undated (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - Source Magazines: Asian arts & culture, undated (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - Source Magazine: Asian arts & culture, undated (Box 13, Folder 133a)
    - Source Magazines: "Eastern Horizon" (Asian arts & culture), undated (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - Source Magazines: BMX bikes, undated (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - Source Magazines: boxing, undated (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - Source Magazines: boxing, undated (Box 6, Folder 137)
    - Source Magazines: boxing, undated (Box 6, Folder 138)
    - Source Magazines: comic books, undated (Box 6, Folder 139)
    - Source Magazine: comic books - "Superman vs. Muhammed Ali", undated (Box 13, Folder 139a)
    - Source Magazines: constellations/astronomy, undated (Box 6, Folder 140)
    - Source Magazines: cops, undated (Box 6, Folder 141)
    - Source Magazines: erotica - firefighters, wrestling, Latin, undated (Box 6, Folder 142)
    - Source Magazines: erotica - women, undated (Box 6, Folder 143)
    - Source Magazines: firefighters, undated (Box 6, Folder 144)
    - Source Magazines: "High Times", undated (Box 6, Folder 145)
    - Source Magazines: hip hop, undated (Box 6, Folder 146)
    - Source Magazines: "Int'l UFO Library Magazine", undated (Box 6, Folder 147)
    - Source Magazines: "Model Railroader", undated (Box 6, Folder 148)
    - Source Magazines: spiritual/mystical, undated (Box 6, Folder 149)
    - Source Magazine: mystical/spiritual (Life: "Visions of Life after Death"), undated (Box 13, Folder 149a)
    - Source Magazines: "Pearl Harbor", undated (Box 6, Folder 150)
    - Source Magazines: prison, undated (Box 6, Folder 151)
    - Source Magazines: skateboarding, undated (Box 6, Folder 152)
    - Source Magazines: skateboarding, undated (Box 6, Folder 153)
    - Source Magazines: "Thrasher" (skateboarding), undated (Box 6, Folder 154)
    - Source Magazines: spanish-language, undated (Box 6, Folder 155)
    - Source Magazine: "El Vocero de Puerto Rico," Feb 2, 1991; Mar 21, 1992, undated (Box 13, Folder 155a)
    - Source Magazines: statue of liberty, undated (Box 6, Folder 156)
    - Source Magazines: tattoos, undated (Box 6, Folder 157)
    - Source Magazines: "Vibe;" "Rolling Stone", undated (Box 6, Folder 158)
    - Source Magazines: wrestling, undated (Box 6, Folder 159)
  - Subseries III.B: Asian-Language Source Material, 1982-1999; .4 Linear Feet in one manuscript box.
    - Chinese-language source material, undated (Box 6A, Folder 160)
    - Chinese-language source material, undated (Box 6A, Folder 161)
    - Chinese-language source material, undated (Box 6A, Folder 162)
    - Chinese-language source material, undated (Box 6A, Folder 163)
    - Chinese-language source material, undated (Box 6A, Folder 164)
    - Chinese-language source material, undated (Box 6A, Folder 165)
    - Japanese-language source material, undated (Box 6A, Folder 166)
    - Chinese-language source material, undated (Box 6A, Folder 167)
    - Source: Chinese script (poster), undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Source: Chinese Newspaper with Chinese Theater Players, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Series IV: Biographical, 1982-1999; 3.3 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons, 2 manuscript boxes, and one oversize flat box
  Series IV: Biographical contains material related to Wong's life and personal. The series includes Wong's curriculum vitae, artist profiles, a copy of Wong's birth certificate and high school reunion program, and his poetry and prose.
  NOTE: Box 7A is labeled "Special Projects"
  - Curriculum Vitae, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Birth certificate, health insurance card, Smithsonian membership, undated (Box 6, Folder 1a.)
  - High school reunion (Class of '64), undated (Box 6, Folder 1b.)
  - Martin Wong shows: invites & P.R. material, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Artist File: compiled by Mrs. Wong Fie (mother) (ca. 1984-1991) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Artist File: compiled by Mrs. Wong Fie (mother) (ca. 1989-1993) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Artist File: Semaphore Gallery, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Clippings about Wong, ca. 1984-1999 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Martin Wong scrapbook, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Martin Wong scrapbook, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Martin Wong publicity photo, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Price lists: Semaphore Gallery (ca. 1985) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Loan agreements for art, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Receipts: for sale/purchase of art, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Floor plan: Wong's apartment, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Leasing & apartment rental, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Apartment purchase: "The Police Building", undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Employment: Metropolitan Museum of Art bookshop, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Worker's compensation policy, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Tax documents (1981) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Medical & health-related, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Sentencing agreement: NYC Parks & Recreation, July 1991 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Draft of Martin Wong catalog, works 1982-1993 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Guestbook (copy): Exit Art Gallery, show "The Social Club," Feb 1988 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Guestbook (copy): "Martin Wong, the Chinatown Paintings," Oct-Nov 1993 (Box 7, Folder 22a.)
  - 1993 mini-appointment book (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Gay & lesbian/AIDS-related, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - "The Village Voice," Jun 27, 1989: "Gay Life 1989" (Box 14, Folder 24a)
  - Personal effects & mementos, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Beatles scrapbook, undated (Box 14, Folder 25a)
  - Portrait of unidentified boy, undated (Box 7, Folder 25b.)
  - Beverly Hillbillies lunchbox, undated (Box 7c, Folder 25c)
  - Paint palette, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - San Francisco Chinese New Year parade, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Chinatown History Museum bulletins, undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Scholastic News bulletins, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Arts journalism: by Theresa Herron, undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Notebook journal (in Latvian - author V. Kuypris?), undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Notes on "Visual Ideas", undated (Box 7, Folder 31a.)
  - Assorted business cards, undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Addresses & phone numbers, undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Contents of Wong's wallet, ca. 1992 (Box 7, Folder 33a.)
  - Writing: "Anti-Gravity for Beginners", undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Writing: "The Darkness" (orig.), undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Writing: "The Darkness" (copy), undated (Box 7, Folder 35a.)
  - Writing: "Das Puke Book," 1977 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Writing: "Find Me the Right Point" (orig.), undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Writing: "Find Me the Right Point" (copy), undated (Box 7, Folder 37a.)
  - Writing: "Firefly Evening," 1968 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Writing: "Footprints, Poems, + Leaves" (n.d.), undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Writing: "Her Lips" (orig.), undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Writing: "Her Lips" (copy), undated (Box 7, Folder 40a.)
  - Writing: "In Search of Holguin", undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Writing: "In the Ring", undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Writing: "The Language of the Fan" (orig.), undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Writing: "The Language of the Fan" (copy), undated (Box 7, Folder 43a.)
  - Writing: "Mojave", undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Writing: "My Story, by Martin Wong" (mini-book), undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Writing: "One Night When" (orig.), undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Writing: "One Night When" (copy), undated (Box 7, Folder 46a.)
  - Writing: "Sister Ed", undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Writing: "Skilling" (orig.), undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Writing: "Skilling" (copy), undated (Box 7, Folder 48a.)
  - Writing: "The Tocci Brothers' Daring Escape" (copy), undated (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Writing: "The Tocci Brothers' Daring Escape" (orig.), undated (Box 14, Folder 49a)
  - Writing: "You Know What I Like About Firemen?", undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Writing: notebook, incl. text on Museum of American Graffiti, undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Writing: scroll, undated (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Writing: mini-notebooks, undated (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Writing: assorted untitled, undated (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Writing: copies of scroll stories, undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Writing: scroll story (orig.), "Nutz Boy: A True Life Story", undated (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Special Projects: Lehman College Phys. Ed. Facility, undated (Box 7A, Folder 57)
  - Special Projects: MTA Arts for Transit poster project, undated (Box 7A, Folder 58)
  - Special Projects: project proposal for Chinatown epic painting, undated (Box 7A, Folder 58A.)
  - Special Projects: Sign Language for the Deaf Project (Box 7A, Folder 58b)
  - Special Projects: I.S. 90 art commissions & school profile, undated (Box 7A, Folder 59)
  - Special Projects: I.S. 90 artist design meetings (minutes), undated (Box 7A, Folder 60)
  - Special Projects: I.S. 90 correspondence, undated (Box 7A, Folder 61)
  - Special Projects: I.S. 90 budget & Wong's notes, undated (Box 7A, Folder 62)
  - Special Projects: I.S. 90 schedule & request for payment, undated (Box 7A, Folder 63)
  - Special Projects: I.S. 90 contract (ca. 1990) (Box 7A, Folder 64)
  - Special Projects: I.S. 90 contract (1992) (Box 7A, Folder 65)
  - Special Projects: I.S. 90 floor plan - entrance gate, undated (Box 7A, Folder 66)
  - Special Projects: I.S. 90 floor plan - first floor, undated (Box 7A, Folder 67)
  - Special Projects: I.S. 90 floor plan - site layout & materials plan, undated (Box 7A, Folder 68)
  - Special Projects: I.S. 90 floor plan - auditorium, undated (Box 7A, Folder 69)
  - Special Projects: I.S. 90 floor plan, undated (Box 7A, Folder 70)
  - Special Projects: I.S. 90 floor plan - cellar & first floor`, undated (Box 7A, Folder 71)
  - "Bay Area Reporter," (gay & lesbian listings), 1991-02-14 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Series V: Video & Sound recordings, 1989-1993; .4 Linear Feet in one manuscript box; 3 videocassettes; 1 audiocassette
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.